Welcome back once again to the ICICI Lomb
presents Brokers Premier League two to
six and the two teams qualified in Group
C Anand United and one l one team Now
it's time for the Group D the four teams I
welcome all the four teams
so I welcome all the teams Gallagher United
United Strikers
ao n and lockten
a on a on ok a on a on a on absolutely
you corrected I said a on a on and on
and lockten welcome everyone.
If we talk about Group A.
So we have Addamed Titans and Pink Panthers
qualified.  Qualified from Group B
are Howden and Budden Warriors
and now qualified from Group C.
One L One Team and Anand Rati United.
First ball of the new match Group D
and this time looking to play for the big one
completely beaten there good by good
fielding they only gave a single
so Gallagher United and United
Strikers news from the centre United
Strikers will be well placed to field
first
going for the second run here the
throw here not so correct two runs here.
Five balls, five runs, no wicket,
Gallagher United
wanted to take runs here but excellent
bowling, end of the over, one over, five runs,
no wicket, Gallagher United,
so if you are a supporter of Gallagher United,
make some noise,
what a thing.  And if you are a supporter of
Unlight Strikers, make some noise.
Good East Side West Side.
Great atmosphere all around here Live
from Fatima Grounds Mumbai under the
floodlights We experiencing one iconic
cricket ground in Mumbai We see the same as
Lords of Mumbai
Mahesh Shetty Only five runs considered Now
Devdas Rane in the attack
Arjun Sharma and Sanjay my two batsmen and
this time what a pick up shot that will go all the way
for four runs Wow
excellent timing very well played So
Gallagher United tell me.  So
beautiful, so elegant, just looking like a.
Wow.  Wow.
Just looking like a wow.  Nine for no loss.
Arjun Sharma has got his first boundary.
And that's a good strike.  The fielder
standing there at long on he drops it he
drops it and two runs taken,
luck favours Arjun Sharma
here, catch missed, dream shattered,
11 runs, no wicket
given, could be a chance of the wicket for the team,
United Strikers
just left to it's a wicket keeper.  That's
very good bowling from Devdas Rane.
Arjun Sharma Sanjay Mehra eight off six
Arjun Sharma with one four and Sanjay Mehra
playing the anchor role
that's a good strike into the gaps that
will run away for four runs
excellent ball excellent batting from
Arjun Sharma
that's what they needed
15 for no loss
no fielder standing at deep cover
last two balls coming up of the second over that will be
the end of the power play after this after this
over
just a single
16 for no loss.  So
what do you want Gallagher United supporters?  We want we want we want let's
see the demand for sixer.  Will Sanjay
Mehra launch a big fireworks
rocket or not.
Last ball second over 16 for no loss.
Oh, here the excellent ball was
missed by the keeper, the back of the fielder was
present there and he stopped it.
So two gone 17 for Nunn Gallagher United
five runs came in the first over then 12 runs came from
this over two overs 17 for Nunn
so waiting for the two more teams to
qualify in into the quarter finals we
already got six teams from group A B
and C and now time for the group D stage
under four teams who will qualify the two
teams in the quarter finals.
I TV
Good shot from Mahesh Shetty Effective
1.2 Only five runs conceded
going down the leg side for wide
waiting for more fire wickets from the team
Gallagher United.
That's very good bowling, just defending it
nicely, got that outside edge for a single.
2.4 20 runs no wicket here Gallagher
United
three runs of the over so far good bowling
o that drop
taken the second attempt and catch dream is
broken but but the face of run out is not
broken.  That's a wicket fall
and if you are a supporter of Unite
Strikers make some noise
where are the supporters of Unite Strikers
?
I think it is very wide.  It is in the corner.
All United Strikers supporters
first wicket fall of Gallagher United.
21 for one
2.5
Priyal Ojha coming at number three
oh wow it's a typical Suryakumar Yadav
shot he played that ends up taking two runs.
That's good running.
So Gallagher United are 23 for one after three overs.   Is
that Devdas Rane once again in the big
attack let's see just
going down the leg side for a wide
left by the batter he is
very flexible
Priya Loja and and Sanjay Mera that's a very
good bowling clever bowling
from Devdas Rane
24 for one the score remains
just a single
looking to flick it but not well timed but will
get a single rans
I looking to play a reverse sweep shot.
What
good bowling from Devdas Rani that's a
very good bowling into the block
hole.  No option left for the battle to just
defend the ball.
26 for one 3.5 last ball coming up of the
fourth over.
Only three runs given in this over Devdas Rani
just chipped in the air but single at long off
so very good over just conceded four runs
Gallagher United are on 27 after four overs
and this time excellent shot.
That will go all the way for six runs.  Wow!
You can see the way he has
created space and played deep backward square
leg.  Hit over the boundary line for six runs.
This is a better angle to watch if you are watching
live on YouTube.
Wow good hit.
33 for two once
again up in an over will they go for two runs
going for two
and excellent
batting is going on here Sagar and Sanjay
35 for two with two runs
on the track very well played
into the gaps and run away for four runs wow
absolutely fantastic batting the number of runs that
Sagar has scored for the team here he has been
successful in batting very well.  12 runs are playing
in four balls 1416
29 for two
and one ball here we have to see umpire
's signal wide ball umpire Mr. Fayariaz
Sheikh so what do Gallagher United want now we want
four runs or six runs we have to see
score is 41 for two last two balls
keeper has missed here will get one bye
and last ball coming up
so what do we expect Gallagher United we want we want
definitely six here Sagar
Mausamkar who had hit a brilliant hit
for six runs a big hit over the backward square
try here last ball
first innings here we go
and yes that's gone for the big one the biggest
of the nine absolutely fantastic from
Sagar here you can see
the action replay
chak de phatte nab de gilli and the ball has been sent
straight to Delhi Khatak
wow
five overs 48 for two amazingly done, made a blast
Sagar Mausamkar has made things miserable I
would like to say that all bowlers
are scared of his arrival  That is Sagar Mausam Kar
ok this is the special moment for the beauty
of trophy reveal moment
hello sir Fayaz sir start a little early
tell the fielding side a bit
quite a big total
49 runs needed in 30 balls let's
see how many runs batsmen Madhav and Mahesh
add for their team in the power play.
OK we have the special moments here.  Sir
welcome to the ICSCI Lamb Brokers
Premier League 226 this is the third edition of
the Mumbai edition and I would like to welcome to
Mr. Ajit Hora. MD & CEO of Galer
Brokers.  Make Some Noise Round Applause.
So first of all Mr. Ajit Hora Sir.  How
is the feeling and what do you want to say?
What you want express in few words?
I think this is awesome.  I I I have not
seen.  Hi.  I think this is um.  I have seen
such a you know insurance companies and
insurance industries tournament of this
level.  Beautiful, awesome.  I cook kiddos to
the ICICI Lomard team and to bring all
these brokers and the entire fraternity
together.  Happy to be here and proud to be here.  Thank
you.
And also we welcome Mr. Irfan Shivani
MD from Team Lockon Company make some noise
round applause
Mr. Irfan Sir few words to express
first of all I really want to
congratulate ICC Lombard for
organizing this event and this is this is
not the first event I am sure this is
I suppose the third season of the third season
and I have been following this season in
every ah year and I am not the player.  I am
of course a big fan of the cricket but I come here
and I watch people playing as a
Mr. Ajit Hura mentioned.  Ah this has this
event has really become a very iconic.  This has become a very you know
branded event.  I
chose not to watch international cricket at home.   I came here to
watch this cricket.  That's the
craze and hype of this.  Really
congratulate me but.
Thank you very much for the few words and I
request sir can you just come for the beauty of
the trophy of the reveal it is time for the
reveal of the trophies the shining trophy will
go to whom and this is the time
celebration of that on
ok in the count of three to one here we
go much
Mr Ajit sir and Mr Irfan sir let's have a big round of
applause for them.
The Diwali The Diwali is still not getting over
[laughs]
The celebration gets
promoted.  Okay thank you very much
one l wanty make some noise
thank you very much.
Fire of the match goes to
even fire crackers the sursuri made the magic
moment funny moments for us.
So 49 to Vinay for one striker and one
over a good start 15 runs on the board
one over 15 runs no wicket 34 from 24
and that's played up played up and over but as a
fielder will stop there will come back for
two
and welcome back in the com box you have
supported us well Om sir from the umpiring also we have
umpiring here if we
talk about commentary then you will not be able to do it.   It
is a very good deposit.  So welcome once again.
Thanks Nitesh.  Tried to play a reverse shot
but missed the ball completely
but could not stop the run.
One over, two balls, 18 runs without
any loss.
49 runs needed in five overs.   The
beginning has been good.
18 runs have been scored in eight balls.
31 runs needed in 22 balls.
Played with light hands. Batsman ran for a run on the on side
but will have to be satisfied with just one run.
Three balls of this over remaining. He
pulled the next ball on the on side, saw the
fielder behind and was caught.
Fall of the first wicket,
one over, four balls, 19 runs and one wicket, it
is a very good view of the ground, floodlights,
outfield, wicket, a
lot of hard work is done here
and what to say about Go Live, it
shows a very good projection.
His cameraman, his team,
all of them are very experienced.   The
next ball of this over, the fifth ball,
wanted to play it towards point but was
completely beaten and Fayaz sir
signaled wide ball, the
score increased to
20 runs, one wicket, two balls remaining in this over,
wanted to play a big shot but completely
missed it,
wanted to play the last ball of the power play towards sweeper cover.
Very good fielding.  Will have to be satisfied with one run.
Two overs, 22 runs, one wicket.
27 runs needed in 18 balls.   Okay, let's
hurry up,
fielding team,
we have less time, let's speed up a bit,
third over of this match,
18 balls, 27 runs needed,
hello and welcome to the four, two more teams are coming,
lockdown and team A on, you are in the final
in the previous season with MI, BL, correct,
so how is your feeling and what would you
like to say in season three?
It's a very good organizing
tournament here last year we played really
well hopefully we will play really good
cricket now and hope for the best may the
best team
okay may the best team wins a on how many
supporters make some noise
okay two are here and the rest of Sri Lanka
[laughs]
okay locken captain how are you feeling
it's a great feeling.  ah I think
it's season three.  I've been fortunate to
partake in all three seasons.  That's a different
story, different organizations.  [laughs]
And been fortunate enough to be a finalist in
season one, but both seasons with different
winners.  Let's hope there's a new winner
this time.  And cheers to our team.  I think we're
prepared.  Let's see the best man
win.
The trophy is very near to you.
[laughs]
ok how many supporters of Locktons big some
noise
so who will declare the winner [laughs]
ok so we will spin the going who will call
from the official will spin Kapil sir
heads is the call from Lockton
tells it is you want the dos what you will
decide
ok I wish you all the best
so after this match we have two new teams
joining the party of group D A on and
Lockton the team A on was
the runner up of
the yest previous year season to
MI BL was a winner of the last season on this
Fatima Grounds
so with that six now 22 runs
needed 13 balls once again
catch has been put down.
Single run taken to end the over.
28 after three overs, 21 runs needed in another two overs.
28 runs after three overs and 21 runs needed in two overs.
That is a bit high in the air but safe landing
umpire signals no ball from leg
and that is coming up follow ball will be
free hit
Rahul on strike
that is a good strike hit hard but the
fielder standing at long off only a
single
18 runs in nine balls with a wide now
17 runs needed in nine balls
this time clever but good bowling
so couple of more good bowling from Ashutosh
Ashutosh Mate
17 runs eight balls
full toss ball but could not take advantage of that full toss ball properly.  Only
one run will be available here.
16 runs and seven balls.
A big hit is essential here.  I can't cross it.
What will the batter do here?
Only a single
they are going for two runs and this will be the easy
run out and yes gone
need 15 runs in one over and keep one wicket
so the final over of the match coming up 15
from six balls here we
go
looking for a big one good stop no runs
15 runs in five balls we have
Devendra Kadu in the big attack
only a one run they need fire wks one run will
not
help them to win 14 runs in four balls 14
from four
will get only a single run
excellent bowling from
Gallagher United.
13 runs needed in three balls.   There
is still a chance 12 runs needed in three balls
Still there is some hope left for Young on
strike to win this match
Mahesh Shetty
on strike
That's gone miles in the air
and that will go all the way for four Still the
hope is remaining
Eight runs needed in two balls There is a chance
here The match has been completely turned around
Now Mahesh Shetty has eight runs in two balls
Need that one ball, a dot ball and one ball A big
hit Mahesh Shetty here we go Eight runs in two balls 0
ball Well left Wow well left Flexible
batsman Mahesh Shetty
Seven runs in two balls
What a match this is 0 That's got a dot
ball
Need that one big hit Last ball 7
runs and one ball
One dot ball will be the match Gallagher United
single double will be also ok
and yes with that